把我藏好
Hide me!
我把埃文的龙之真气逼出来了
I unleashed Evan's inner dragon
现在根本收不回去了
and now I can't put it back in its cage.
帕克在哪里啊
Where's Parker?
我的猛龙想要把他乱丢一气
My dragon wants to throw him around some more.
我什么都不知道  小伙子
No idea what you're talking about, son.
老头  别想忽悠我
Don't lie to me, old man.
我看见他在你后面发抖了
I can see him trembling behind you.
我不是说过不能在屋里乱跑吗
What did I say about running in the house?
我不是说过不能乱搭话吗  女士
What did I say about talking back, woman?
站定  简直激动死了
Stop, drop and howl.
爸  《太空狼人》导演组来电话了
Dad, the "space werewolves" movie people called,
很明显  我的视频火了
and apparently my video went viral.
他们唯一比免费宣传更喜欢的
And the only thing they love more than all the free publicity
就是你拍的免费照片啊
were all the free pics you took.
我成功回到主演的候选名单了
I'm back on the short list for the lead.
我真为我的小狼人感到骄傲啊
I'm so proud of my little werewolf.
啊
Aah!
克制住你的龙  克制住你的龙
Cage your dragon! Cage your dragon!
嗨  埃文
Hi, Evan.
噢  对哦
Oh, right.